nmrdirect.com 2008-12-12

# National Marketing Resources

**Privacy Policy Statement for National Marketing Resources**

Protecting our visitor's privacy is a priority for National Marketing Resources. The following policy represents our commitment to ensuring that your personal information is protected and your concerns regarding the management of your data are addressed and honored. Please send us an email if you have any questions regarding this policy.

This policy covers the following areas:

  1. Contact Information (How to Reach National Marketing Resources)
  2. Information We Capture and Collect
  3. Opt Out Instructions
  4. Future Changes to This Policy
  5. Correcting Your Contact Information
  6. Security

**Contact Information**

National Marketing Resources  
351 West Washington  
Kearney, Missouri 64060  

We can be reached via email at: [Privacy@NMRDirect.com](mailto:privacy@nmrdirct.com)

**Information We Capture and Collect**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes the customer's domain name, referring URL when possible, but not any personally identifying information.

We collect only the email addresses of those who communicate with us via email, aggregate information on what pages customers access or visit, and information volunteered by the customer, such as survey information and/or site purchases or registrations.

The information we collect is for us to use to communicate with customers regarding our products and services, and to improve the content of our Web pages. 

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to record session information, such as items that customers add to their shopping cart.

**Opt Out Instructions**

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please let us know by sending us email at [Privacy@NMRDirect.com](mailto:privacy@NMRDirect.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page. You may also use the opt-out instructions found at the bottom of every email communication from us to remove your address from our list. We will respect your request for privacy, and will remove your address from future email communications. (Note: please allow up to 7 business days for your request to be fully processed).

Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online may receive telephone contact from us with information regarding new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by sending an email to Privacy@NMRDirect.com, or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.

**Future Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by sending an email to [Privacy@NMRDirect.com](mailto:privacy@NMRDirect.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.

**Correcting Your Contact Information**

Upon request we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in their contact information. Customers can have this information corrected by sending an email to [Privacy@NMRDirect.com](mailto:privacy@NMRDirect.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.

**Security**

With respect to security, we use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving customer data exchanged with our site. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that National Marketing Resources does not own or control, or to people that National Marketing Resources does not employ or manage. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us by sending an email to [Privacy@NMRDirect.com](mailto:privacy@NMRDirect.com), or by writing to us at the address listed at the top of this page.
